Horikita joined the student council,
but I haven't gotten any
new information out of her.
Nagumo's personal maneuvering aside,
the management of the student
council appears to be above-board.
The real action started
on a particular weekend,
one week before the deadline
for forming groups.
The vice president, Kiriyama,
had asked to speak with me.
So here we are.
Classroom of the Elite 4th Season 2nd Year 1st Term
How can I help you, Mr. Vice President?
The deserted island test starts
at the end of the month.
#8 The Subject of the Dragons' Gaze
Have you completed your preparations?
I've done what I can.
What about you, Vice President Kiriyama?
I'm thinking of engaging in an
individual fight in the upcoming test.
An individual fight?
Our class lost the battle with
Nagumo and was dropped down.
He's gradually taking control
of the whole school.
There's no more fighting our class can do.
The only thing I can do is settle
things on an individual basis.
I understand.
But I'm not sure why you would
want to tell me about that.
Let's just say I don't want
any outside interference.
Outside interference?
You sent Horikita-senpai's
sister into the student council
to keep an eye on Nagumo, didn't you?
I can't say that wasn't part of it.
Though it's not the main reason.
It's so that Horikita can walk
the same path her brother did.
You won't get in my way, then?
As long as Horikita doesn't
see Nagumo as an obstacle.
I can't accept that.
Nagumo is aware on some level that I was
leaking information to Horikita-senpai.
Any unwarranted interference now...
It could put you in danger?
Yes.
Are you looking for a chance
to move up to Class A?
What's the point of graduating
in anything but Class A?!
I refuse to go down with the
incompetents and weirdos of Class B!
Kiriyama.
You're with an interesting
underclassman, I see.
Ayanokoji Kiyotaka, right?
Spending time with someone like
that won't get you anywhere.
Better than spending time with you.
That's up to Ayanokoji
to decide, I'm sure.
That's Kiryuin. She's in Class B with me.
I saw her OAA.
A highly-regarded student with Academic
Achievement and Physical Ability of A+.
She does well on paper.
But she doesn't have supporters
like Nagumo does.
She doesn't have a single real friend.
Listen to those compliments.
You're making me blush.
Engaging with her is a waste of time.
What's wrong? You won't come to see me?
I think she wants to talk to me.
If you don't come to me,
I'll have to come to you.
Are you sure you want that?
People like her are why I've
had to settle for Class B.
She's a selfish outsider who
doesn't care about anyone else!
Thank you for the compliment.
I'd like to talk to Ayanokoji.
You're in our way.
Don't forget what I said.
Watch your step, or I'll
become your enemy, too.
Standing to talk is so
uncivilized. Let's sit.
Sure.
So, what did you want to talk to me about?
Anything at all.
I just want to get a read on you.
A read on me?
The reason you don't
contribute to your class is
because you aren't interested
in your classmates, right?
What I'm not interested in is this
school's system of competing for Class A.
I'm talented enough on my own merits to
get whatever position I want after school.
You wouldn't have come here if
you'd known it was like this, then?
Far from it.
I like this school.
And the point system affords
me a comfortable life.
You've been asking all the
questions, you know...
Why me, though?
There are lots of students here
with high Academic Achievement.
Instinct.
My instinct tells me that
you're extraordinary.
Are you going to try to take first
place in the upcoming survival game?
I'm sure every student
wants to take first place.
Except people like you, Kiryuin-senpai.
Maybe not first, but I am aiming
for one of the top slots.
A top slot will earn
me more private points.
Money tends to burn a hole in my pocket.
I never seem to have enough.
The upcoming special test
is also a battle to determine
the best student in the school.
Whether or not my interest
in you is misplaced
will be determined by your
achievement on the island.
I think I'd rather not have
you interested in me.
You do say the most interesting things.
I'm looking forward to fighting you,
Ayanokoji.
Well, well. The loyal dog has
returned with its master in tow.
What was that?
Hey, don't say hurtful things
to my dear colleague.
Dear colleague?
I'm not sure I buy your sincerity.
It's entirely genuine, I assure you.
Now, Mr. President. How can I help you?
I didn't think we had any more business.
I certainly don't intend to stay long.
Despite your beauty,
you're entirely lacking in charm.
I have no interest in women like that.
Oh, I have a great many charms.
I just haven't met the gentleman
who could draw them out of me.
I'd love to see the man who could.
As would I.
I really wonder why the
men aren't all over me.
Men don't know how to
deal with a strong woman.
I see.
If they're all just intimidated,
I completely understand.
You've been taking good
care of your hair, I see.
I'm sure the women are all over you.
Had any better luck in the romance
department these last three years?
A woman who's never dated a man
wants to comment on my love life?
There's no need to be ashamed
of a lack of experience.
Couldn't you actually say
it makes me more valuable?
As usual, your mind works
in the strangest ways.
Kiriyama told me what you said.
You've never shown any interest
in me or Horikita-senpai,
yet you've set your sights on
Ayanokoji? Very unexpected.
You seem to be under a misapprehension.
I'm really quite interested in people.
When someone sparks that interest,
I'll happily approach them.
You and Horikita Manabu, too... I was
interested in you both at one point.
And what do you make of Ayanokoji?
I'm reserving judgment for now.
I lost interest in you,
but I think he'll be more fun.
You're the only one who could
openly insult me like that.
I'd love to rein in that
arrogance of yours.
When you lose, your losses will
be beyond measure, Mr. President.
Let's call it aura.
I sensed an aura about him different
from that of you and Horikita Manabu.
That's not very concrete.
Why not test him, then?
I intend to.
We may see what he can really
do on the upcoming island test.
I said I was reserving judgment
on Ayanokoji Kiyotaka earlier...
but I do think he's an
interesting student.
Oh?
You see the underclassmen
as amusing playmates.
But if you really went for it,
you'd take first place, no doubt.
Oh, there's no question of that.
Either me or my rival Kiriyama.
But if we want to sweep all three top
spots, we'll need another group, won't we?
You should take that role, Kiryuin.
I see. So that's what you wanted.
But you have countless other
pawns to call upon, don't you?
You're not interested, then?
So sorry to waste you a trip.
I should have expected no less.
It was a waste of time, then.
Since you went to the trouble to come
here, I'll offer you a word of advice.
Don't worry about the underclassmen.
Just focus on your path forward.
You may end up burned.
What a ridiculous thing to say.
Off to Keyaki Mall this early?
I won't have time to relax
once the test starts.
Ichinose seems to trust you a lot.
Is that trust justified?
We've canceled our alliance,
but I don't view Ichinose as an enemy.
Kanzaki...
Are you trying to get some kind of
comment from me to pass on to Ichinose?
You're far sharper than we ever thought.
I can see that Class D's
rapid rise is because of you.
You think so?
I want to ask for your help.
Ichinose trusts you greatly.
I want you to tell her that she
needs to change her approach.
You really think that
will get her to change?
Yes.
Sorry, but I can't help you there.
I want to see where Ichinose's
approach takes her.
And, fundamentally, it's up
to us to help our own classes.
Don't you think?
True. Maybe I'm trying
to defer responsibility.
I feel like I've had the answer I need.
But I'm grasping for alternatives because
I don't want to go through with it.
This is a rather random grouping.
I'd like to know why you called us here.
Just relax already.
I couldn't possibly relax.
I don't even want to be
seen in your company.
What's Class A's plan in the
deserted island survival game?
What do you mean?
Do you have your sights set
merely on class points alone,
or something else?
And the fact that Ichinose and Shibata
are in a group with Sakayanagi
stinks to high heaven.
Would this be a new alliance?
You're free to interpret
it however you like,
but I won't tell you a single thing.
Don't be so uptight, Katsuragi.
You'd like it if Sakayanagi got expelled
in the upcoming test, wouldn't you?
What?
If she went away,
Class A wouldn't have a leader.
You'd be back on top then.
I don't know what you're
planning, but it won't work.
Sakayanagi has enough points
to save herself from expulsion,
and she can use her
protection point, as well.
True, getting her expelled would
require at least two strikes.
The idea of doing it in the
next test was a joke, anyway.
The deserted island survival game
isn't a place to take down enemies.
It's a place to advance yourself
through your own power.
What really matters is that Year 2
doesn't lose any class points.
To do that, I need a few allies.
Surely you're not proposing
an alliance with me?
Not just you.
The quiet listener over there, too.
Ayanokoji.
Huh? Me, too?
You thought I called you
out here for nothing?
He has impressive math skills, but do
you really think he's suitable for this?
An understandable concern
from a position of ignorance.
But my strategy is the right call.
This man beat me once before, after all.
Is that true?
Admit it, Ayanokoji.
Even if I did, do you think
I would work with you?
Not easily, I'm sure.
Unbelievable.
I see you weren't serious
about this from the start.
Have you forgotten that,
since last year's island test,
the contract you made with
me has obliged Class A
to send me large numbers
of points every month?
I'm sure that doesn't sit right with you.
But you can't take revenge because
you know it's your fault.
Join Class B, Katsuragi.
Ridiculous.
If you don't have the money, I'll pay up.
Even so, you expect me to
abandon the prestige of Class A?
I'll be bringing down
Sakayanagi very soon.
Once that happens, her class
will enter a downward spiral.
Ryuen Kakeru
Katsuragi Kohei
You remember this, don't you?
The contract we signed last year.
Yes.
I negotiated with Sakayanagi and
let her out of it for five million.
You won't get another chance like this.
Why would you do all of this for me?
You don't think very highly of yourself.
But it's true,
I'm shelling out a lot here.
I've already collected the remaining
points needed from my class.
Go on and sign it already.
Class Transfer Contract
July 10th
First Party: Advanced Nurturing High School Class 2-A
Second Party: Advanced Nurturing High School Class 2-B
Ryuen Kakeru
You're serious?
See it as fate, and accept it.
What do you expect from me?
Am I allowed to give my opinions freely?
Do what you like.
Even your uptight opinions will
be useful from time to time.
By the way, Ayanokoji.
What in the world are you doing?
Oh?
Well... I was wondering how my
coffee would taste if I diluted it
three or four times over.
You're a strange man, Ayanokoji.
What about him, then?
If we let a Class D student into the
group, it will halve our reward.
I didn't say we were
letting him into the group.
I want you to sell us the
Trial card you were dealt.
On one condition.
Trade your Halve card for the
Bandwagon card in our class.
If Kei ends up taking a penalty, she can
use Halve to keep it in the safe zone.
It's a deal.
What are you going to do for your group?
The deadline's coming up.
Working alone will let
me be more adaptable.
But if you end up in poor health,
you'll fail on the spot.
The penalty is severe.
You'll be expelled.
You haven't formed a group
yet either, have you?
You and I have different risk levels.
Last year, you got sick before
the deserted island test.
I think you should form a
group of two for insurance.
But the only two left in the
class are you and Koenji-kun.
I have a lead on someone
from another class.
Huh?! You want me to work with Horikita?
Yeah, pretty much.
Her physical abilities are acceptable,
but everything else is cause for concern.
Hey, you can't talk to me like that!
Ishizaki, did you know this was
what they were going to ask about?
What's the big deal? No one
else will pair up with you.
But I hate this guy.
And I hate Horikita even more!
I won't work with her.
Excuse me. I don't recall
agreeing to work with you.
Huh? What's that supposed to mean?
You're alone because you
were the odd man out.
I was always intending to fight alone.
Although we're both alone,
our situations are drastically different.
I wanted to do this alone, too!
Besides, if we're both
singles, that's perfect.
Let's compete, Horikita.
May I ask a question?
Why are you so opposed to me?
We've had our differences, but I don't
recall giving you a reason for bad blood.
You're the only one who thinks that.
I see this was a waste of time.
Hey, get back here!
Are we competing or not?!
I won't necessarily stick
to a solo strategy.
Once the test starts, I may
join other groups as necessary.
So lame.
The special tests are too important
to worry about appearances.
Even if I join a group,
I hope you'll work hard.
If you still beat me,
I'll give you some credit.
Fine by me!
1st Term Closing Ceremony
Schedule
1. Opening speech
2. National anthem
3. Message from acting chairman
4. Speech by student council president
5. School song
6. Closing speech
The end-of-term ceremony
came and passed in a flash.
Soon, we'd be heading out for the
deserted island survival test.
This won't be your first time
undertaking a special test.
You've spent over a year at this school,
facing and overcoming challenges.
But the test you're about to face will
be harsher than any you've faced before.
I'll make just one request of you—
if possible, I want every one of you
back in this classroom when it's over.
Horikita, my girl.
May I talk to you about the test?
That's unusual.
Have you decided to voluntarily
participate at last?
Let's say you're half right.
I know you desperately want the class
points awarded to the top three groups.
Naturally.
Let's make a deal, then.
If I make a good showing,
will you promise me total freedom
in the class until graduation?
That's quite a bold proposal.
You're asking me to indulge your
selfishness moving forward?
Exactly.
Like a full advanced payment
through graduation.
It seems even you're feeling
a sense of desperation.
I'm sorry, but a decent effort
from you isn't worth the trade.
No room to negotiate, then?
No, but I can't accept a vague offer
like "make a good showing."
You must take first place
in the year by yourself.
If you can't, you must promise to work
with us on the next special test.
Yes, very well.
I shall agree to your terms.
You have yourself a deal,
Horikita, my girl.
July's half over already.
It's gotten quite hot.
The doubts over Chairman Sakayanagi's
conduct will also be clearing up soon.
It will become difficult for
me to remain in my position.
All the more reason...
I've prepared a grand
fireworks show for the finale.
I'd like you to use any means necessary
to have Ayanokoji Kiyotaka
expelled from the school.
Is that understood?
Yes. I've put my doubts behind me.
I'm counting on you...
Nanase Tsubasa-san.
Yes, sir.